(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-20T05:30:35.512645",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Seasons From Within #Myth6thAnniversary
[Seasons From Within - Myth 6th Anniversary]
#Myth6thYears
営みの 街が暮れたら色めき
When the bustling town grows dim and colorful,
風たちは運ぶわ カラスと人々の群れ
the winds carry the crows and crowds of people.
意味ない夜に 暮らしがあるだけ
In meaningless nights, there is only daily life;
ただ腹を空かせて 君のもとへ帰るんだ
just emptying my stomach, I return to your side.
物心ついたら ふと見上げて思うこと
When I came to my senses, I suddenly looked up and thought,
この世にいる誰も ふたりから
everyone in this world starts from two people.
胸の中にあるもの いつか見えなくなるもの
What's inside our hearts, what eventually becomes invisible—
それは側にいること いつも思い出して
always remember that it's being close by.
君の中にあるもの 距離の中にある鼓動
What's inside you, the heartbeat within the distance—
恋をしたの あなたの指の混ざり ほほの香り
I fell in love, your fingers intertwining, the scent of your cheeks.
夫婦を越えてゆけ
Go beyond being a couple,
美しとひそめた想いは色づき
The feelings we secretly called beautiful take on color,
白鳥は運ぶわ 当たり前を変えながら
and white swans carry them, changing what we take for granted.
恋せずにいられないな 似た顔も虚構にも
I can't help but fall in love, with familiar faces and illusions alike.
愛が生まれるのは ひとりから
Love is born from a single person.
胸の中にあるもの いつか見えなくなるもの
What's inside our hearts, what eventually becomes invisible—
それは側にいること いつも思い出して
always remember that it's being close by.
君の中にあるもの 距離の中にある鼓動
What's inside you, the heartbeat within the distance—
恋をしたの あなたの指の混ざり ほほの香り
I fell in love, your fingers intertwining, the scent of your cheeks.
夫婦を越えてゆけ
Go beyond being a couple,
泣き顔も 黙る夜も 揺れる笑顔も いつまでも いつまでも
Tearful faces, silent nights, swaying smiles, forever and ever.
泣き顔も 黙る夜も
Tearful faces, silent nights,
揺れる笑顔も いつまでも いつまでも
swaying smiles, forever and ever.
いつまでも
Forever and ever.
胸の中にあるもの いつか見えなくなるもの
What's inside our hearts, what eventually becomes invisible—
それは側にいること いつも思い出して
always remember that it's being close by.
君の中にあるもの 距離の中にある鼓動
What's inside you, the heartbeat within the distance—
恋をしたの あなたの指の混ざり ほほの香り
I fell in love, your fingers intertwining, the scent of your cheeks.
夫婦を越えてゆけ
Go beyond being a couple,
ふたりを越えてゆけ
go beyond two,
ひとりを越えてゆけ
go beyond one!
皆さん！皆さん！
Everyone! Everyone!
Hey, hey! What's up everybody?
Welcome. Fell out of order.
Welcome. We fell out of order.
Yes. Welcome, welcome, welcome!
自己紹介！自己紹介！I am Mori Calliope of Hololive Myth.
Self-introductions! I am Mori Calliope
of Hololive Myth.
Really? Does that really count? Sympathy by like, what, an hour, half an hour or so?
Really? Does that really count?
Sympathy by an hour, half an hour?
So be it. 皆さん, it is I, Mori Calliope of Hololive Myth.
So be it. Everyone, it is I,
Mori Calliope of Hololive Myth.
Lost Child. Four is my favorite number, but six is good too, my goal...
Lost Child. Four is my favorite number,
but six is good too. My goal...
Come here. Anyway, yoroshiku! And who's next?
Come here. Anyway, yoroshiku!
And who's next?
Kikkeriki! I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive Myth!
Kikkereki! I am Takanashi Kiara
from Hololive Myth!
How's it going? It's 6 years!
And I am surrounded by Myth, Myth, Myth, Myth, Myth!
And I am surrounded by Myth,
Myth, Myth, Myth, Myth!
That's my introduction. I still don't have anything in particular. I'm 6 years!
That's my introduction. I still don't
have anything in particular. I'm 6 years!
What about you? Do you have a special introduction? Yes, she does.
What about you? Do you have
a special introduction? Yes, she does.
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
Good morning, afternoon, evening,
everyone!
Ninomae Ina'nis of Hololive Myth, on this wonderful day!
Ninomae Ina'nis of Hololive Myth,
on this wonderful day!
Yay! On this wonderful day!
She was shaking her legs earlier, she was scared. I was not scared!
She was shaking her legs earlier,
she was scared. I was not scared!
It's going to be okay. Don't dance too hard, you know. If you dance too hard you could fall.
It's going to be okay. Don't dance
too hard. If you dance too hard...
Yeah. Okay, everybody, congratulations on 6 years! Shake those hands!
Yeah. Okay, everybody, congratulations
on 6 years! Shake those hands!
Shake those hands, shake those hands! And check it out, after all this time...
Shake those hands! And check it out,
after all this time...
We also have... we've all done live shows!
We also have... we've all done
live shows!
Look at the solo outfits! We all have solo outfits! So cute!
Look at the solo outfits! We all
have solo outfits! So cute!
Kaela, you've done a lot in these 6 years, huh? Done a lot, huh?
Kaela, you've done a lot in these
6 years, huh? Done a lot, huh?
I feel like 6 years ago we never would have even thought that we could do that.
I feel like 6 years ago we never
would have thought we could do that.
Do you guys still remember the very first time we met each other on Discord?
Do you guys still remember the very first
time we met each other on Discord?
Yeah, it was so weird. The introduction channel, where like everybody typed like a paragraph about themselves.
Yeah, it was so weird. The introduction
channel, where everybody typed a paragraph.
And you didn't mention drawing at all, so we were all so surprised! She was hiding it even from us!
And you didn't mention drawing at all!
She was hiding it even from us!
But that made it even more impressive. So, so, so.
But that made it even more impressive.
So, so, so.
This stream is supposed to celebrate our 6 years together. And we have a hashtag for that too.
This stream is supposed to celebrate
our 6 years together. Hashtag for that!
Right here, #Myth6Years. Use it a lot on Twitter, etc.
Right here, #Myth6Years. Use it
a lot on Twitter, etc.
Capture your favorite moments and share them with us, because we look at that stuff, you know.
Capture your favorite moments and share them,
because we look at that stuff, you know.
For 6 years, her hips danced so healthily, okay? Dancing hips for you guys, smoother and smoother.
For 6 years, her hips danced so healthily.
Dancing hips for you guys, smoother.
And we want you guys to take pictures of them! Yes! Beautiful pictures because not only are we wearing our beautiful outfits, but we also have a beautiful stage, right?
We want you to take pictures! Beautiful outfits,
and we also have a beautiful stage, right?
High up in the sky. And, and, and I get a feeling that the seasons will change...
High up in the sky. And I get
a feeling that the seasons will change...
Depending upon the songs that we sing. That's probably true.
Depending upon the songs that we sing.
That's probably true.
And we already showed them a little bit of the seasons with the first song that we performed, "Calliope"!
And we already showed them a little bit
of the seasons with our first song, "Calliope"!
I like that we're doing this one because we did the sun-covered one too. And it was really good.
I like that we're doing this one because
we did the sun-covered one too.
I really like how it turned out. There are all these cute scenes with us like cooking together and hanging out.
I like how it turned out. Cute scenes
with us cooking and hanging out.
No, I'm not into lollipops. You have your own lollipop. You already linked it, I don't want it.
No, I'm not into lollipops. You have your own
lollipop. You already linked it!
We got found out. Gakki-gakki!
We got to perform! We can't eat too much kinpaku-soft right after a live show. So, dayo.
We got to perform! We can't eat too much
kinpaku-soft right after a live show.
Speaking of the sassy lass child that we have here, huh? She's so small!
Speaking of the sassy lass child
that we have here, huh? She's so small!
She told us she notices it to calm down.
Can we just say that in our solo outfits, Gura has never been this small in comparison before.
Can we just say that in our solo outfits,
Gura has never been this small before.
They nerfed my height! That's so funny!
Are you really this tiny? Like our gaki cousin, little cousin, or something like that.
Are you really this tiny? Like our
gaki cousin, little cousin, or something.
Are we here aunties, her mommies, or her sisters?
Are we her aunties, her mommies,
or her sisters?
Can we go to... I can't say that. Yamero!
Can we go to... after this? No, no, no, we can't. We have that at home.
Can we go to... after this?
No, we can't. We have that at home.
But Ina-chan, you know what? At the end of the stream we'll have a surprise for you and everybody else!
But Ina-chan, you know what?
At the end of the stream we'll have a surprise!
And you won't want to miss it, so make sure that you behave for the entire live!
You won't want to miss it, so behave
for the entire live stream!
Don't break the cameras this year. Oh no! Now stand until the end, Ina and San.
Don't break the cameras this year. Oh no!
Now stand until the end, Ina and San.
Till the end everybody is in there too, okay!
はじまる
It's starting.
You're safe this time, Calli.
Anyway, what could it be?
Oh boy!
Let's go!
All right, shall we?
いこう！
Let's go!
Yeah!
Let's do this! Next song!
辛い色のシャツ 追いながら
Chasing a shirt the color of dried leaves,
飛び乗った電車のドアは
the doors of the train I jumped on
いけないと知りながら
knowing I shouldn't,
振り向けば隠れた
when I looked back, they had vanished.
街には色付いた クレヨンが
In the town, colored crayons
涙まで染めて走る
run, dyeing even my tears.
年上の人に出会う
Knowing it was a promise
約束と知っていて
to meet someone older,
セプテンバー そしてあなたは セプテンバー
September... And you, September...
秋に変わった
changed into autumn.
夏の日差しが 弱まるように
Like the summer sunlight fading,
心に影が差した
a shadow fell across my heart.
セプテンバー そして九月は セプテンバー
September... And September...
さよならの国
is the land of goodbyes.
ほどきかけてる 愛の結び目
The knot of love coming undone
涙がこのはになる
turns my tears into leaves.
会ってその人に 頼みたい
I want to ask that person when I see them
彼のこと返してなと
to give him back to me.
でも駄目ね 昨日の弱さ
But no, yesterday's weakness...
唇噛むのこの上で
biting my lip right here.
セプテンバー そしてあなたは セプテンバー
September... And you, September...
秋に変わった
changed into autumn.
話すことさえ なくなるなんて
That even talking became impossible
私に起きた証拠
is proof of what happened to me.
セプテンバー そして九月は セプテンバー
September... And September...
さよならの国
is the land of goodbyes.
巡る季節の 彩りの中
In the colorful turning of the seasons,
一番寂しい好き
it's my loneliest favorite time.
借りていた ピクショナリ
I'll return the Pictionary
明日返えすわ
I borrowed tomorrow.
ラブという 言葉だけ
Only the word 'love'
切り抜いたあと それが答え
cut out... that is the answer.
セプテンバー そしてあなたは セプテンバー
September... And you, September...
秋に変わった
changed into autumn.
私ひとりが 傷つくことが
That I alone am the one who gets hurt
残された優しさね
is the kindness left behind.
セプテンバー そして九月は セプテンバー
September... And September...
さよならの国
is the land of goodbyes.
取り戻すの 海の縁の服も
The clothes by the water's edge
二度と着ることはない
I'll never wear again.
しゅびどぅびどぅびどぅわわ
Shooby-dooby-dooby-doo-wop
セプテンバー
September...
ララナラララ ララララ
La la la la la la la la...
気づけば 靴は汚れ
Before I knew it, my shoes were stained,
錆び付いたもろさは 伝う雨
the rusted fragility trickling down like rain.
憧れは そのままで
My yearning remained just as it was;
夢から覚めた先には夢
beyond waking from the dream was another dream.
聞こえた その泣き声
The weeping voice I heard,
消えている手前の無邪気装われ
feigning innocence just before it fades away—
憧れの その先へ
heading beyond that yearning.
薄くなる君を見つけるため
To find you as you grow faint,
ゆけ ゆけ 追い付けない速度で 飛べ
go, go, fly at a speed I can never catch!
インパルス 加速して ゆけ
Impulse, accelerate and go on.
きっとこのトクベツを感じるため 生まれてきたんだ
I must have been born to feel this specialness.
未来を選んで 期待値を超えて 期待に行き交う風
Choosing the future, surpassing expectations, winds crossing paths with hope.
今に見なよ きっと君の眩しさに 誰もが気づくだろう
Just you wait, surely everyone will notice your brilliance.
相応しい声で 視線も越えて 虚空を超えてゆく
With a fitting voice, surpassing gazes, crossing the void.
見えていく君の影から今 手を離す
Now, I let go of your fading shadow.
気づけば 謎は解かれ
Before I knew it, the mystery was solved,
黙々目録と見慣れた板の上
upon the familiar stage with a silent catalog.
あの頃 焦がれたような 大人になれたかな
I wonder if I've become the adult I once yearned to be.
そう君の苦悩は 君が自分で選んだ痛みだ
Yes, your anguish is the pain you chose for yourself,
そして掴んだ形の金も 全て君のものだ
and the money you grasped in that form is all yours.
僕は夢になって 君が喋っただけのやっとで強く引いた
I became a dream, barely pulling strongly at what you spoke of.
今君は決して風に流れない 矢になって
Now you become an arrow that will never be swept by the wind,
ゆけ ゆけ 決して振り向かないで 飛べ
go, go, never looking back, fly!
もっと届かない場所へ
To a place even further out of reach.
きっと君はいつだって輝いていた
Surely you were always shining no matter when.
未来を選んで 期待値を超えて 期待に行き交う風
Choosing the future, surpassing expectations, winds crossing paths with hope.
今に見なよ きっと君の眩しさに 誰もが気づくだろう
Just you wait, surely everyone will notice your brilliance.
相応しい声で 視線も越えて 虚空を超えてゆく
With a fitting voice, surpassing gazes, crossing the void.
見えていく君の影から今 手を離す
Now, I let go of your fading shadow.
初めてのキスは 涙の味がした
Our first kiss tasted of tears,
まるで空一面の星空みたいな恋
a love like a sky full of stars.
瞬く間に伝うよ はしゃぎあったように
Passing by in the blink of an eye, just like when we laughed together.
話そ 伸びるがな
Let's talk...
初めての恋が終わる時
When our first love comes to an end.
冷たい冬の風が 頬をかすめる痛い
The cold winter wind stings as it brushes my cheek.
泣き出しそうだよ 流って僕歌う
I feel like crying, so I sing like this.
魔法をかけたみたい 裸足が痛いの ジュキラキラ
like magic casting a spell—my bare feet hurt, sparkling.
街はイルミネーション
The town is illuminated,
クラシックでも 嫌だった この気持ち
Even classical music—I hated this feeling,
押さえつけてきた
holding it down.
前から決めていたことだから これでいいの
This is what I decided long ago, so this is fine.
すてきな恋だった
It was a wonderful love.
ありがとう さようなら 切ない片思い
Thank you, farewell, my painful unrequited love.
足を止めたら 思い出してしまう
If I stop my feet, the memories will come back.
だから ありがとう さようなら ないた寂しいから
That's why, thank you, farewell, because crying is lonely.
そう思ったとたん ふわり
The moment I thought that, softly,
舞い降りてくる雪 触れたら溶けて消えた
the fluttering snow touched me, melted, and vanished.
描きあと続く踊り
The dancing footprints go on,
寄り添ってるふたり楽しそう
two people snuggling close, looking so happy.
ほら見て 初雪
Look, first snow.
君とあんなふうになりたくて
Wanting to be like that with you,
初めて作った出会いのマップ
the map of our meeting that I made for the first time,
どうしたら果たせたんだろう
how could I have ever fulfilled it?
口なしの恋は
A voiceless love
壊れかけた
was falling apart.
思い出になるならこのままで構わないってそう思っていたの
If it becomes a memory, I thought I'd be fine staying this way.
魔法本当なの
Is magic real?
ありがとう さようなら
Thank you, goodbye.
いつかこんな時が来てしまうこと分かってたはずだわ
I should have known such a time would come someday.
なのに ありがとう さようなら
Even so, thank you, goodbye.
からだがぶるえてる
My body is trembling.
もうすぐ列車が来るのに
Even though the train is coming soon,
それは今になって私を苦しめる繋がっていたい
now it tortures me—I want to stay connected.
どれほど願い続けただろう
How much did I keep wishing?
この手を離さずにいようね
Let's never let go of these hands.
ありがとう さようなら
Thank you, goodbye.
繋がってちゃそんなの分かってる
If we stay connected, I already understand that.
君が優しいことも知ってる
I know that you are kind too.
だから言葉を話してよ
That's why you speak the words.
出会えてよかった 君が好き
I'm glad I met you, I love you.
ありがとう さようなら 一言が言えない
Thank you, goodbye—I can't say those words.
いまだけでもいい 私に雪を
Just for now, give me snow.
言いかけた唇の君との距離までの
The distance of our lips as we approached...
今だけは泣いていいよね
I can cry right now, right?
もう言葉はいらない 骨がぎゅっとしていて
No more words needed, hold me tight.
最後の今頃には どんな私がいて
At this very last moment, what kind of me will be here?
どんな君がいるのかな
What kind of you will be there?
Whoa, you got some extensions!
Extensions? I don't remember getting anything like that.
Your hair is even longer!
Heh, it's fashionable though, don't you think?
It looks kind of familiar.
Oh, like girl, maybe we're missing some...
Oh, you have another arm, too?
Whoa, there. Hold on a second, I'm trying to explain.
You're going out? Not only has music-
You're going out? Not only has music—
Oh, I lost time!
But it looks like we've lost somebody.
Welcome back!
Hi.
Hello.
You're here, you're here.
E ine, nice nice hair.
Eh ne, nice, nice hair.
The seasons have changed. Yes, it's getting a little warmer, thank goodness.
It was kind of cold, you know? It's a little chilly, especially for me and Kiwawa's song.
It's become spring! Wow, beautiful!
Check it out, the stage is so pink. I actually really like the color pink now, after these six years.
Character development.
The seasons have changed. That's good, that's good.
And we're wearing Yukata kimonos, whatever you wanted it to be.
And we all went for kind of a blue color, right?
Yeah, we do look like we're about to drop a sweet enka album.
Dokko-sho, dokko-sho! Soran, soran!
Soran, soran, soran!
Okay, that's not what we're doing. We're not releasing those.
So we did a bunch of songs, like, for example...
For example, September... that's not the one that you sang! No, please, please wait! This is a really iconic old...
日本の歌、オッケー？
Japanese song, okay?
結構ポーズ
Lots of poses!
うんうんうんうん
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was so cute. I hope you guys enjoyed this old tune. Yeah.
Right?
Yeah Ina, did you, did you, did you know it before?
Yeah Ina, did you know it before?
No.
No? Kelly, did you know it before?
No? Calli, did you know it before?
No? First time hearing it.
I think first impression.
I think everyone in the chat will also agree. Have you heard the word September, we
No, no, no. This is how we change the impression of September.
When we say September, you guys will think of that September anymore. You think about this September with me and Ina, okay?
When we say September, you won't think of that September anymore. You think about this September with me and Ina, okay?
Yeah, just for now.
What else was did we perform? Oh, I also saw you did some
What else did we perform? Oh, I also saw you did some...
ballet skating moves. Are you a filthy archer?
I'm disgusted by you.
You hate archer. I hate archer.
You hate archers? I hate archers.
Archer, such cheaters. I've never seen this anime, but is there actually an archer in there?
Archery is for cheaters. I've never seen this anime, but is there actually an archer in there?
Yeah. Really? No. Oh no, there are skaters though.
Skaters.
Figure skating. Oh, I can. I can do it.
I'm all right. I can skate, too. Okay.
She goes somewhere. Really? We should go. We should go.
I can skate. I used to go skating. That was my favorite hobby when I was younger.
It's a promise. Well, anyway, I loved your low tones.
Yes, and yours was truly a heart.
Yes, and yours was truly heartfelt.
No, no, no. It came out beautifully. Your song wonderful.
No, no, no. It came out beautifully. Your song was wonderful.
And I got to sing with Kiara as the snow fowl.
And I got to sing with Kiara as the snow owl.
We talked and sang a song about first love.
And weren't we so cute? If this boy happens and first love and and
And weren't we so cute? If this boy happens and first love ends...
Takamori, it feels wholesome to me. I don't know.
Chikateme mwah mwah no kissu mwah mwah mwah mwah kissu kissu mwah
How did that how did that make you feel everybody in the chat? What do you think about
How did that make you feel, everybody in the chat? What do you think about it?
Were you jealous or were you happy for us? Love and Think carefully about your answer.
Were you happy for us? Totally okay.
Thank you.
They're definitely saying yes.
Well, we have also changed costumes.
We're so blue and pink. White, blue, pink, yellow, red, white and blue, and blue and blooms. Not quite.
Austrium and Milswiro cause I lost purple Purv. Nobody Ah, soda ne.
Austrium and Milswiro because I lost purple Purv. Nobody... Ah, sodane!
Wait, is this morning glory? Ah, I thought we were jellyfish.
Jellyfish? No, I think it's morning glory.
Morning glory! It could be any it could also be Austrian bread called Semmel. That's exactly the shape of Austrian bread.
Morning glory! Or it could also be Austrian bread called Semmel. That's exactly the shape of Austrian bread.
Did the breads come in those colors?
No, only unless maybe if they're moldy. Hope you never eat one of those. Don't eat moldy bread.
We know you're here aware of that. Have you eaten moldy bread before everybody? Are you sure? Stale bread. Why is this what we're talking about during our concert?
We know you're aware of that. Have you eaten moldy bread before, everybody? Are you sure? Stale bread? Why is this what we're talking about during our concert?
It's okay. A little whimsy is fine.
But now, how about we get serious for a moment and sing a kyoku song? Kyoku, kyoku, let's sing a kyoku.
But now, how about we get serious for a moment and sing a kyoku song? A kyoku... let's sing a kyoku.
That's the yamereta. Stop it! Let's sing a song that's a little bit emoy.
That's yamereta. Stop it! Let's sing a song that's a little bit emo.
I was listening to the lyrics and practicing it and I was like, you know, there are a couple of lyrics here and there that remind me of like the struggles that we have gone through and and how I want to go forward with you guys.
I was listening to the lyrics and practicing it and I was like, you know, there are a couple of lyrics here and there that remind me of the struggles that we have gone through and how I want to go forward with you guys.
So, it made me kind of like uh emo. So, I hope we can sing it well together. Yeah, we will.
And and these slightly restrictive will be a very really stretchy outfits.
And these slightly restrictive—well, they're really stretchy outfits.
Okay, enough of that.
All right, now we can start the show and sing. All right, listen to our next song, Suzume.
君の中に ある赤と青き線
The red and blue lines inside you...
それらが結ばれるのは 心の臓
...that tie them together are the heart.
風の中でも負けないような声で
With a voice that won't lose in the wind,
届ける言葉を今は育てている
I am now cultivating words to send out.
時はまきふぐり 風はにきはだ 星はうぶすな 人はかげろう
Time is fleeting, wind is gentle, stars are sacred, man is ephemeral.
なんて泣いているのかと聞かれ答えられる 涙なんかじゃ
When asked why I'm crying, I can answer: it's not just tears.
僕ら出会えたことの意味にはまるで追いつかない
They could never catch up to the meaning of us meeting.
君の中にある
Inside you
赤と青き線
are red and blue lines.
風の中でも負けないような声で
With a voice that won't lose to the wind,
届ける言葉を今は育てている
I am now nurturing words to deliver.
時はまぐう 風はにきはじ
Time is fickle, the wind is gentle,
星はうぶすな 人はかげろう
Stars are a birthplace, people are fleeting.
なんで泣いてるのって聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, I can answer,
涙なんかじゃ
that it's not just tears—
僕ら出会えたことの意味には まるで
It's almost as if the meaning of us meeting
追いつかないこの身ひとつ
is far beyond this single self—
じゃ足りない叫び
a cry that isn't enough.
君の手によれたときにだけ震えた
Only when I touched your hand did I tremble,
心があったよ
there was a heart.
意味をいくつ越えれば僕らはたどり
How many meanings must we cross to reach
つけるのかな おろかさでいい
where we're going? It's okay to be foolish,
みそかでいい
it's okay to be clumsy.
正しさのその先で 君と手を取りたい
Beyond correctness, I want to take your hand.
思い出せない 大切な記憶
Important memories I can't recall,
言葉にならない
unable to put into words—
ここにある重い
the weight that is here.
もしかしたら もしかしたら
If by chance, if by chance,
それだけてこの 心はできてゆく
just with that, this heart is formed.
もしかしたら もしかしたら
If by chance, if by chance,
君に気づいて どういまもその胸を 打ち鳴らす
noticing you, even now, that chest rings and resonates.
なんで泣いてるのって聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, I can answer,
涙なんかじゃ 僕ら出会えたことの意味にはまるだ
that it's not just tears—the meaning of us meeting...
追いすかないこの身ひとつ じゃ足りない叫び
a cry that isn't enough for this unreachable body.
君の手によれたときにだけ震えた 心があったよ
Only when I touched your hand did I tremble, there was a heart.
君をいくつ越えれば僕らはたどり
How many of you must I cross to reach it?
つけるのかな おろかさでいい
Wondering if we'll arrive. It's okay to be foolish,
みそかでいい 正しさのその先で 君と手を取りたい
it's okay to be clumsy. Beyond correctness, I want to take your hand.
君と生きたい生きたい
I want to live with you, live with you.
SAKURA Days (feat. AO)
[Title: SAKURA Days (feat. AO)]
離れる怖さとらされるすべてが愛おしい
The fear of parting and everything captured are so dear.
背伸びの心もヒラリいては また思いふける
Even my stretching heart flutters as I fall into thought once again.
桜 Days
Sakura Days
一瞬の風に揺れていた髪が なつかしい
The hair swaying in a fleeting wind brings nostalgia.
賑わいと温もりを運んでくれた おかげでいろざいた花
The flowers that bloomed thanks to bringing hustle and bustle and warmth
有るものは恋い焦がれて 有るものは皆で分かち合い
Some things are yearned for, some things are shared by everyone.
千本の一夜差しを巡る雲の音の舞い散る
The dance of clouds and sounds surrounding a thousand nights' offerings fluttering down
舞い散る 夜風に触れた 切な果がわし
The poignant fruit touched by the night breeze...
さようならとありがとう共に送るよ おかげでまた好きになった
Saying goodbye and thank you together, thanks to you I've come to love it once more.
去るものを追えるはずなく
There's no way to chase what's leaving,
来るものは拒めるわけない
And no way to reject what's coming.
優劣遠い
Superiority and inferiority are far away...
桜舞い散る日の日々よ
Oh, days of cherry blossoms falling and scattering!
離れる覚悟　悟らされる全てが愛おしい
Everything that makes me realize the resolve to part is so precious.
セピアの心情を開いては　また思い耽る
Opening up sepia-toned feelings, I muse on them once again.
SAKURA Days
遥か彼方響く君の声に耳をすませば
If I strain my ears to hear your voice echoing from afar,
少なからずその温もり思い出せるよ
I can still recall that warmth to some extent.
凛とした寂しさも　風情と成る
Even a dignified loneliness turns into elegance.
桜Days
SAKURA Days
桜Days……
SAKURA Days...
少なからずその温もり思い出せるよ
I can still recall that warmth to some extent.
麗しき桜Days
Beautiful SAKURA Days
本気ボンバー！！
Honki Bomber!!
夏じゃん見上げる空　青い海
It's summer! Look up at the sky and the blue sea!
自由に描こう　僕がルール
Let's draw freely, I am the rule!
夏じゃん大きくなれ　本気ボンバー！！
It's summer, grow big, Honki Bomber!!
好奇心のまま GO!
Go with your curiosity!
熱くなれ！
Get fired up!
遊びも百点！
100 points in play!
学びも百点！
100 points in studies!
時間で一杯　手もどかない
Packed with time, can't even get my hands on it—
ボンバー！不運のせいや絶対しない　そもそも人生成長いつの連続
Bomber! I'll never blame bad luck. After all, life is a continuous growth!
夏じゃん頼れるヤツ　キザなヤツ
It's summer! A dependable guy, a flashy guy.
いろいろ出会い　僕が育つ
Encountering all sorts of things, I grow.
夏じゃん成長しろ　本気ボンバー！！
It's summer, grow up, Honki Bomber!!
世界みんなで Peace! 立ち上がれ！
Everyone in the world, Peace! Stand up!
涙も出る！
Tears come out too!
拍手もする！
We applaud too!
褒めて褒められ　やる気も出る！
Praising and being praised, it builds motivation!
ボンバー！タブーも無しだって夢があるだろう
Bomber! Even without taboos, there must be dreams!
いつかは青空の彼方へと
Someday to the beyond of the blue sky,
夏じゃん見上げる空　青い海
It's summer! Look up at the sky and the blue sea!
自由に描こう　僕がルール
Let's draw freely, I am the rule!
夏じゃん大きくなれ　本気ボンバー！！
It's summer, grow big, Honki Bomber!!
好奇心のまま GO!
Go with your curiosity!
熱くなれ！
Get fired up!
夏じゃん頼れるヤツ　キザなヤツ
It's summer! A dependable guy, a flashy guy.
いろいろ出会い　僕が育つ
Encountering all sorts of things, I grow.
夏じゃん成長しろ　本気ボンバー！！
It's summer, grow up, Honki Bomber!!
世界みんなで Peace! 立ち上がれ！
Everyone in the world, Peace! Stand up!
夏じゃん見上げる空　青い海
It's summer! Look up at the sky and the blue sea!
自由に描こう　僕がルール
Let's draw freely, I am the rule!
夏じゃん大きくなれ　本気ボンバー！！
It's summer, grow big, Honki Bomber!!
好奇心のまま GO!
Following curiosity, GO!
熱くなれ！
Let's get fired up!
YO! SAY夏が 胸を刺激する
YO! SAY, summer stirs my heart,
生足 魅惑の マーメイド
bare legs, a bewitching mermaid.
出すここと出して タワワになったら
Showing what should be shown and becoming voluptuous,
本物の恋は ヤレ爽快っ!
true love is, oh, so exhilarating!
ゴマカシきれない 薄着の曲線は
Unmistakable, thinly-clad curves
確信犯のしなやかな STYLE!
are a deliberate, graceful STYLE!
耐水性の 気持ちに切り替わる
Waterproof feelings take over
瞬間の一瞬さは いかがなもの
in a fleeting moment, whatever that may be.
ココロまで脱がせる 熱い風の誘惑に
Enticed by the hot wind that strips down to the soul,
負けちゃいけないから 真夏は
you mustn't lose, so midsummer is...
不祥事も キミ次第で
and even scandals depend on you!
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies stimulate the summer,
生足 魅惑の マーメイド
bare legs, a bewitching mermaid.
出すここと出して タワワになったら
Showing what should be shown and becoming voluptuous,
本物の恋が できそうかい?
can you make it true love?
君がなくても パッと君にもなるよ
Even without you, it'll suddenly become about you,
熱いバカの 街は憂鬱で
the city of passionate fools is gloomy.
スキを見せたら フニミミに入る
If you show an opening, it creeps into your ears,
寒いギャグなんかで すべりたくない
I don't want to bomb with some cold gag.
着替える ネタいやを
Changing diamond-like outfits,
彩る 花火のように
like colorful fireworks,
打ち上げて散る 想いなんだ
my feelings shoot up and scatter.
このまま 抱き合って
Just like this, embracing and
焦がれるまで
until we burn up.
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies stimulate the summer,
生足 へそだし マーメイド
bare legs, midriff-baring mermaid.
出すところ出して 素直になったらに
Showing everything off and becoming honest,
君と僕となら いつも All right!
with you and me, it's always All right!
都会のビルの 海じゃ
In the ocean of city buildings,
感じなくなってる ヒミツを
the secrets you've stopped feeling
気だるい インノクチ
lazy innocence,
続けて 弱らせて 惑わして
keep it weak, bewitch it,
差し上げましょう
I'll treat you to it.
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies stimulate the summer,
生足 へそだし マーメイド
bare legs, midriff-baring mermaid.
恋に免れて オルスになるのも
Being excused for love and being away,
大スキ的にも おれ OK!
even with my favorite, I'm OK!
妖精たちと 夏を誰としたくなる
Who do you want to spend summer with?
一人での夜に 救急セイブワイ
On a lonely night, an emergency save why
奥の方まで 乾くまないもの
dry all the way inside, something that never dries,
本物の恋を 示せよ Savior!
show true love, Savior!
Super Sentai!
Super Sentai?
I don't know, maybe that's our Super Sentai move.
No, no, no!
Like this? Like this? No, it was sexy!
Okay, sexy, sexy, Sentai!
Sexy Sentai, sexy Sentai!
That's cancel Sentai!
Wow!
Sexy, sexy, sexy! Oh, where did we go?
Okay, welcome back, everybody!
Hey, welcome back!
Hello!
How did you guys think? Having a good time?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Sang some awesome songs!
Yeah! Yeah!
So many good songs!
Yeah, some very close to my heart. Limit very hot.
Limit to the hotness!
You were already too hot, yeah.
Past the hot, makes sense, yeah.
Absolutely. If you were on the stage, everything would've lit on fire.
Absolutely. If you were on stage, everything would've caught fire.
Yeah, there's a lot of cheese here. What the fuck?
I don't know. If we die, it will be better.
I don't know. If we die, it'll be better.
And I did my solo "Mahibomba," which is a hell of a project song.
And I did my solo "Mahi Bomber," which is a hell of a project song.
I had to squeeze in one more "Helloween Project" song. I hope you like it.
Yeah, yeah, maybe perhaps some people recognize it, you know?
Yeah, maybe some people will recognize it, you know?
And you did a solo? - I did, "Sakura Days."
Because that song is what is a song that I did at my very first ever singing stream six years ago...
Because that song is a song that I performed at my very first singing stream six years ago...
...and and I could not...
I either sang it super low or super high, and this time I was like, "I want to really like sing it with my whole heart."
I either sang it super low or super high, and this time I was like, "I really want to sing it with my whole heart."
And so that song is really special to me and I hope you guys enjoyed "Sakura Days."
Enough of that!
And then also that was a good reaction.
Okay, who's next shift of folks?
Okay, who's the next shift of folks?
I don't know. Cinnamon. Cinnamon, we need Cinnamon.
Cinnamon. That was a while. Yeah, yeah.
Really beautiful. Yeah, we looked really cool together and the stage was lovely as well.
And we went through some extra seasons, right? We did.
And we went through some extra seasons, right? - We did.
We went through summer. Uh-huh. We're in summer right now, I don't know.
It's a little hot, so probably definitely summer. It's going to cool down from now, you guys, definitely.
Will it get even hotter? - Yeah. - Well, perhaps this was a sign.
This is, however, our PR section, isn't it? We have to show something to you guys, right?
So first and foremost, I'll start, I'll start. Oh, it's okay. Don't don't everybody all go at once. I will begin.
So first and foremost, I'll start, I'll start. Don't everybody go all at once. I will begin.
As you guys know, I had my own little solo show in VR, and at that time, I promoted to you guys this year's Mori Calliope 6th Anniversary Goods.
Yatta!
Yay!
Check 'em out, check 'em out!
Can I join in? - No, no, no, no, no!
All right, I feel left out right now, but that's okay, we can go on.
If you are a fan of Mori Calliope Dead Beat, I'm looking at you. I have an official happi coming out. It's my very first happi! It's really, really cool.
If you are a fan of Mori Calliope, Deadbeat, I'm looking at you. I have an official happi coming out. It's my very first happi! It's really, really cool.
I wanted to emphasize something that's very kakkoii, like cool darkness, and like there's the illustration of me on the back looks like a painting, and it's really cool.
I wanted to emphasize something that's very *kakkoii*, like cool darkness, and like the illustration of me on the back looks like a painting, and it's really cool.
Not quite, it's like it's like haft annive have very like illustrative. So I hope you like it, there's big skull on the front, it's awesome.
Not quite, it's like half-aniki, very illustrative. So I hope you like it, there's a big skull on the front, it's awesome.
Yeah, and then Deadbeats officially get a headband, because I know you guys want to get their headband.
In addition to that, I have a bag, bag that has... What color is the bag? - Black, of course.
In addition to that, I have a bag, a bag that has... What color is the bag? - Black, of course!
And it's got a little window in it, you can carry one with like a black bag with window.
And it's got a little window in it, you can carry one with a window, a black bag with a window.
And penlight holder! Penlight holder, very important.
And a penlight holder! A penlight holder, very important.
And a little place where you can put your badges, and I have four random badges that you can get.
So yeah, please buy the goods!
Now, also, my latest music video, "Dandé Compassis" out right now.
Now, also, my latest music video, "Dandé Compass," is out right now.
So I have a brand new 3D outfit, I do lots of dancing, I have some cool backup dancers that are real people behind me, so it's really cool.
Yeah, and it's it's Mori in the real world, and I also I'm really big, I'm like a kaiju also, so it's really awesome.
Yeah, and it's Mori in the real world, and I'm also really big, I'm like a kaiju too, so it's really awesome.
Yes, so please make sure you watch that. And also finally, Chadcast has begun again. Yes, me and Iris and Bae, uh we also have a music video for our theme song too, so don't miss out on that.
Yes, so please make sure you watch that. And also finally, ChadCast has begun again! Yes, me and IRyS and Bae, uh we also have a music video for our theme song too, so don't miss out on that.
That's all that I have for PR.
Oh, that's all? Are you sure there's no more?
It really is, it's really it. I know there's a lot of stuff. Sorry! Let's go to Ina.
Ina, well, I just revealed, or I guess last week revealed my new outfit.
And with that I also released my sixth anniversary merch.
Acrylic block, a cup and saucer, you can put coffee in it too.
An acrylic block, a cup and saucer. You can put coffee in it too.
And then there's a mini plushie of me in the new outfit.
Acrylic block.
Acrylic, acrylic—
Yeah, thank you, thank you!
Yo, let's go! Yeah, and of course,
Hololive's, um, very first Project: FINALLY!
Finally! At last! Want to Bijou him every day!
Let's go! Check it out! Very high quality, beautiful. Don't miss out.
It's releasing. To be released? I don't know.
This is past puff. It's probably out.
Past puff? Don't know. Likely out. Big chance it's out.
If it's out, watch. If it's not, get ready! Yeah! Let's go!
And last but not least, Takanashi Kiara!
This year has no anniversary merchandise, no solo, and no group, so I have nothing.
I also don't have a song coming out either. Thank you, wait. It's okay. There's a gift from you guys to me and from me to me, which is I'm taking a break— thank you!
Take a good rest. Come back strong. Yeah, please welcome me back when I do come back.
And yeah, please just wait for me. Don't forget about me. Yeah!
But you can still support me in a way by supporting all of us because we now finally can say we have a new song coming out.
We will perform it now, and it will premiere after this. We will raid you into it, but in case the raid doesn't work, make sure to jump in there on your own. It will be on this channel.
Yeah. It will be on this channel. 99% sure. Yeah. Are you excited?
Get hyped! They're excited. I can sense it. It's very cool. Hold on, we're wearing this outfit. This doesn't mean I have to move a lot.
Yeah! Oh yeah! Bring it around town.
So, are you ready? You ready? I know you can do it, Ina. Come on. Let's do it.
Alright. Mori! Come on! This is me!
Let's go. Stay for the premiere, guys.
THIS IS MYTH
[Title: This Is Myth]
Stand up, shout it, ask the audience, do y'all feel it?
Start up, have it, go on, take a guess, yeah, what's the name?
Myth!
Been here from the start, we laid the groundwork,
Had a spark, now look, it's an inferno,
No, no, won't say sorry,
We paved the way, built it from zero,
You get the memo.
Mythologically, you're still tryna figure out how my mind navigates where you couldn't.
Try and find where we're about, but know ya goin' down.
It's destiny, it's not a stroke of luck,
Can't you see that it was meant to be us all,
Chikinima, yeah, you know just what to do,
If you want us, say it loud like M-Y-T-H.
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in, we the best, the rest can't imagine.
How pretty, I'm sittin' here up at the top, goin' nonstop, show ya what we got.
Make ya stressed out, bet you been sweatin'. What's our next move? We'll leave you guessin'.
We don't trip up and we never stop, had to remind ya in case you forgot.
Myth! Now and then, we the best, so yell it like, Myth!
I can hear 'em go, this is our myth.
It ain't a surprise that we pulled up took the win, from the very start, made the biggest impression.
Now we got crowds beggin' for us on stage, yellin' out like, they'd all die for me.
We unstoppable, it's our reputation, you can bet on forever, we ain't done.
Try and find what we about, but know ya goin' down.
It's destiny, it's not a stroke of luck,
Can't you see that it was meant to be us all,
Chikinima, yeah, you know just what to do,
If you want us, say it loud like M-Y-T-H.
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in, we the best, the rest can't imagine.
How pretty, I'm sittin' here up at the top, goin' nonstop, show ya what we got.
Make ya stressed out, bet you been sweatin'. What's our next move? We'll leave you guessin'.
We don't trip up and we never stop, had to remind ya in case you forgot.
All the struggles everyday, every mistake, what we lost and gained, it's fair.
We can't be shaken up, no, we'll keep going on and on and on and on.
We're not afraid 'cause we lead the way,
And when it's silent, we can (welcome to our universe)
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in
We the best, the rest can't imagine
How pretty I'm sittin' here up at the top
Goin' nonstop, show you what we got
Make ya stressed, I bet you been sweatin'
What's our next move? We'll leave you guessin'
We don't trip up and we never stop
Had to remind ya, in case you forgot
Uh-huh, uh-huh uh-huh
Now and then, we the best! So, yell it like
MYTH!
Uh-huh, uh-huh uh-huh
I can hear 'em go
This is our myth!
Thanks a lot, everyone!
Thank you!
See ya!
Happy 6th Anniversary!
Kill the music video!
Oh my god!
We're rating you!